{
    "subject": "resource/All_American_Chump",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "All American Chump is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9721326231956482,
            "question": "Is 'All American Chump' considered a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7833767533302307,
            "question": "What type of media is 'All American Chump'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35247963666915894,
            "question": "Can you name another film that is also a type of Film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2643251419067383,
            "question": "Give an example of a film genre."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21956230700016022,
            "question": "What makes a film different from other types of media?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21051013469696045,
            "question": "Are there subgenres within the 'Film' category?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19403143227100372,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16126728057861328,
            "question": "What are some popular film genres?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16073624789714813,
            "question": "What is the purpose of filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.051356784999370575,
            "question": "How has technology influenced film production?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=All American Chump is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5983_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the purpose of filmmaking?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5983_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular film genres?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5983_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common characteristics of films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5983_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5983_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5983_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5983_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5983_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5983_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5983_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5983_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5983_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5983_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5983_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that \"All American Chump\" is indeed a film, as it includes details such as its director, running time, and cast members."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}